[{"id": "596760e12b59efe0e9417e9e", "question": "Panophobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "Everything", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a4ea", "question": "What did the letters in USSR stand for?", "answer": "Union of Soviet Socialist Republics", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a337", "question": "Which actress was dubbed \"The Scream Queen\" after appearing in numerous horror films?", "answer": "Jamie Lee Curtis", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe3e92f38e4e5d4832e630f", "question": "What was the infamous Bloody Mary's occupation?", "answer": "Queen", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be04", "question": "What position was first held by Steve Allen?", "answer": "Tonight Show host", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe0de8bfcbed638185eaa16", "question": "In which US state is Crater Lake found?", "answer": "Oregon", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "58ab979f86faa38a764be52a", "question": "What is the Wankel engine typically referred to as?", "answer": "Rotary engine", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59ded323ea2747c8aff16d45", "question": "What is a \"Sam Browne\"?", "answer": "Military belt", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5eb738325e259d786908732e", "question": "What book by George Orwell had a film adaption that was funded by the CIA?", "answer": "Animal Farm", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339fc1", "question": "What genre is Iggy Pop considered to be the grandfather of?", "answer": "Punk", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c6aa", "question": "What is the chemical symbol for the element Magnesium on the periodic table?", "answer": "Mg", "category": "science"}, {"id": "59008adbcf842fa4c4ba9694", "question": "What is the name of the lively Spanish dance in triple time and typically performed with castanets or tambourines?", "answer": "Fandango", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b686", "question": "Figure skater Elvis Stojko comes from which country?", "answer": "Canada", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339616", "question": "Alfred Hitchcock's 1948 film \"Rope\" was based on a real-life crime committed by who?", "answer": "Leopold & Loeb", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe6a1b620565ad31a57c7a5", "question": "What was the first US state to have two female senators at the same time?", "answer": "California", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d29", "question": "What sport is the focus of the movie \"The Stratton Story\"?", "answer": "Baseball", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe7349eeec85e375820b239", "question": "The Colossus of Rhodes was dedicated to which god?", "answer": "Helios", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ae83", "question": "Which highwayman rode a horse named Black Bess?", "answer": "Dick Turpin", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391a3", "question": "What color is Shrek?", "answer": "Green", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fd96e9e23c87fd04dd15e3a", "question": "As of 2020, who was the last human to walk on the moon?", "answer": "Eugene Cernan", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b13f", "question": "How many months did it take the Mayflower to cross the Atlantic Ocean?", "answer": "2", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c4aa", "question": "The star Polaris is more commonly known by what name?", "answer": "The North Star", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a5c5", "question": "What is the official state animal of the US state of Oregon?", "answer": "The beaver", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "6014c5dafbde8045e48466b1", "question": "An \"unkindness\" refers to a group of what animal?", "answer": "Ravens -- They have a bad reputation, and have been considered bad omens for centuries.", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bceb", "question": "Cap'n Crunch's flagship is named for what fish?", "answer": "The guppy", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a982", "question": "Which island of Japan is just 26 miles form Russia at its closest point?", "answer": "Hokkaido", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fea782dff048f679a45abd4", "question": "If a doctor told you there was fluid entering your lungs, what term might he use to describe this?", "answer": "Aspiration", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113397be", "question": "What 1980's band had fans that happily called themselves \"blockheads\"?", "answer": "New Kids on the Block", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c640", "question": "By what name is Sodium Chloride better known as?", "answer": "Salt", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd14", "question": "What was the original brand of cereal whose mascot was CinnaMon?", "answer": "Apple Jacks", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339afc", "question": "What did Billy Batson have to shout in order to turn into Captain Marvel?", "answer": "Shazam!", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d1a", "question": "A lock of what composer's hair was sold at one of Sotheby's Auctions?", "answer": "Beethoven's", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b2bb", "question": "Which of Henry VIII's wives was married four times herself?", "answer": "Catherine Parr", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe7bd35877e98cb97778956", "question": "What African country served as the setting for Tatooine in Star Wars?", "answer": "Tunisia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "6002449b4be4723ccac221a6", "question": "What artist is known for having painted the Moulin Rouge?", "answer": "Henri de Toulouse-Lautrec produced a collection of provocative images of the decadent life of 19th century Paris.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fefc4dd6ce05a3942286f38", "question": "What is the name of the fishing boat that is featured in the film \"The Perfect Storm\"?", "answer": "Andrea Gail", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "60077f9fbd51d85e222ab63e", "question": "What late 19th-century French painter was known for his pictures of ballet dancers?", "answer": "Edgar Degas is acknowledged as the master of drawing human figures in motion. The female ballet dancer became his favorite theme.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a4f4", "question": "What US state has the longest border with Canada?", "answer": "Alaska", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133beaa", "question": "What cousin of the glockenspiel was named for its ethereal, \"heavenly\" sound?", "answer": "The celesta", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c49d", "question": "Self-rising flour contains what crucial ingredient?", "answer": "Baking powder", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339502", "question": "What movie includes the quote, \"That rug really tied the room together\"?", "answer": "The Big Lebowski", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bdfd", "question": "Whose famous balloon says \"State Fair Omaha\" on the outside?", "answer": "The Wizard of Oz's", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe7d5e3877e98cb97778a66", "question": "In the movie \"Batman v Superman\" what poster can be seen in the background as the Waynes are walking out of a movie theater before their mugging?", "answer": "The Mark of Zorro", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b767", "question": "What country traditionally goes last in the Olympic opening parade?", "answer": "The host country", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fecd0c4ec223966ae8f88bb", "question": "What is the only Star Wars film in which Harrison Ford receives top billing?", "answer": "\"Star Wars: The Force Awakens\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b62f", "question": "In the Western Union's alphabet what is the letter \"C\" known as?", "answer": "Chicago", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b553", "question": "How many official jelly belly flavours are there?", "answer": "40", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59ca3dbb44f0f6af5b06663e", "question": "What is the capital of Andorra?", "answer": "Andorra la Vella", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a605", "question": "Vienna and Belgrade lie on the banks of which river?", "answer": "The Danube", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133aef6", "question": "What killed over half a million Americans in 1918?", "answer": "The Influenza epidemic", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c4bf", "question": "In medicine, what does the abbreviation LASIK stand for?", "answer": "Laser-Assisted In Situ Keratomileusis", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5ff51ce2ff04d658268c931d", "question": "Who invented the rubber band?", "answer": "In 1845, Stephen Perry, of the rubber manufacturing company Messers Perry and Co., invented the rubber band.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b6df", "question": "What flavor is Grand Marnier?", "answer": "Orange", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ffb69055dad637d903c8845", "question": "In which national capital can you find around 200,000 gers (traditional round tents) alongside other kinds of\u202fhousing?", "answer": "Ulaanbaatar, Mongolia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113398c2", "question": "What is Mickey Mouse's dog's name?", "answer": "Pluto", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe7c961877e98cb977789f4", "question": "Which state boasts the world's largest flat-top mountain?", "answer": "Colorado", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a83", "question": "Which original \"Star Trek\" character was played by James Doohan?", "answer": "Scotty", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe767f8eec85e375820b29c", "question": "Which city is considered the birthplace of democracy?", "answer": "Athens, Greece", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd6b", "question": "In photography, what kind of \"number\" is used to measure lens speed?", "answer": "f", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ffb5b835dad637d903c881b", "question": "What is the most-popular meat served on Christmas in the United Kingdom?", "answer": "Turkey meat", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe65934ae7e414034b5aefc", "question": "What killer was known as the \"Vampire of Dusseldorf\"?", "answer": "Peter Kurten", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bfaa", "question": "James Hunt was disqualified after winning which Grand Prix?", "answer": "1976 British Grand Prix", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ab6b", "question": "What country is East Pakistan now known as?", "answer": "Bangladesh", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a618", "question": "The underground lake, The Lost Sea, is located in which US state's Craighead Caverns?", "answer": "Tennessee", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba14", "question": "Carl Lewis won gold medals in what event at four consecutive Summer Olympics?", "answer": "Long jump", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133926b", "question": "What singer was the first Latin-American actress to be paid $1 million for a movie role?", "answer": "Jennifer Lopez", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133aeb1", "question": "Over what part of Captain Robert Jenkins were Britain and Spain at war in 1739?", "answer": "His ear", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133997b", "question": "In the TV show \"The Simpsons\", what is the name of Lenny's ex-wife?", "answer": "Emma", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba13", "question": "What position did football hall-of-famer Dick Butkus play with the Chicago Bears?", "answer": "Linebacker", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b29d", "question": "What US president loved Fresca so much he had a soda tap installed for the Oval Office?", "answer": "Lyndon Johnson", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339bb2", "question": "What band's 1993 debut album was entitled \"August and Everything After\"?", "answer": "Counting Crows", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5941281cbab1e6f9796f1b5a", "question": "In what sport with animals do you find \"coursing\"?", "answer": "Greyhound racing", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5990f4c4fa5fdd6dd25324e5", "question": "What country borders Central African Republic to the north?", "answer": "Chad", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "6003950057a0e35c43f83890", "question": "What is the term for a thin, opaque coat of paint or layer of shading applied to give a softer or duller effect?", "answer": "Scumble - A technique in which the coating is opaque, and is painted on thinly to allow bits of the paint below to shine through.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c17e", "question": "What is the name of the leading female singer in an opera?", "answer": "Prima donna", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a0cb", "question": "Whose debut solo album was entitled \"Schizophonic\"?", "answer": "Geri Halliwell's", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59a7f64f6f5f79087132fb43", "question": "Which actress who played Alia Atreides in 1984's \"Dune\" and went on to star in 1998's \"Urban Legend\"?", "answer": "Alicia Witt", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a78", "question": "What William Faulkner novel presented its plot from four different points of view?", "answer": "The Sound and the Fury", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5990aefbb72eedf883a8c703", "question": "In what collection of sports would you use spikes and blocks?", "answer": "Athletics", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bae1", "question": "In what country was the International Red Cross founded?", "answer": "Switzerland", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133aeac", "question": "Who was the second president of the United States?", "answer": "John Adams", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe7bd0c877e98cb97778952", "question": "What river runs through Baghdad?", "answer": "Tigris", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b6a7", "question": "Facebook was originally developed as a social tool for students at which university?", "answer": "Harvard", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a9d", "question": "What movie marked the feature film debut for Rene Russo?", "answer": "Major League", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5909d0e1bb53d1af658864fe", "question": "The \"Christmas Price Index\" tracks the cost of what items?", "answer": "The gifts in the song \"The Twelve Days of Christmas\"", "category": "general"}, {"id": "600f6e97a9e54d890926f6c7", "question": "Just off the coast of Venezuela, one will find Aruba, Bonaire, and Cura\u00e7ao, collectively known as what?", "answer": "The three islands are collectively known as the ABC Islands, or Dutch Antilles.", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ae37", "question": "What international award did President Theodore Roosevelt win in 1906?", "answer": "Nobel Peace Prize", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bb69", "question": "What tennis player was named \"Sexiest Woman in the World\" by FHM magazine in 2002?", "answer": "Anna Kournikova", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5b323204bf195a31e15d738b", "question": "Belmopan is the capital of which country?", "answer": "Belize", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5ffa3acfc73aa70ea0b70ae1", "question": "What is the highest waterfall in Europe?", "answer": "The\u00a0Krimml Waterfalls", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b54f", "question": "How many Bits are in one Byte?", "answer": "8", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fd66959a5bfecdd737e087a", "question": "Who was the last king of Troy in Greek mythology?", "answer": "Priam", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a196", "question": "In the video game \"God of War\", which mythological character must Kratos defeat at the end to finish the game?", "answer": "Ares (the God of War)", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c6c", "question": "What is the name of the sequel to the 1977 movie \"Saturday Night Fever\"?", "answer": "Staying Alive", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fd81b39d0de9af39e9d4676", "question": "What ancient people created massive head figurines out of boulders?", "answer": "The Olmec", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5a9e95c97ccba3ffe45786e4", "question": "What alcohol do you mix with lemonade to make a Snowball cocktail?", "answer": "Advocaat", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c7a", "question": "Which duo created the Indiana Jones character?", "answer": "George Lucas and Steven Spielberg", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339fd8", "question": "What TV show did \"Young Americans\" spin off from?", "answer": "Dawson's Creek", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b74e", "question": "What is the highest number on a standard roulette wheel?", "answer": "36", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba3a", "question": "Thomas Jefferson is depicted on what US coin?", "answer": "5 cent coin", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113399d2", "question": "Which ghost did Carol Kane portray in the 1988 film \"Scrooged\"?", "answer": "Ghost of Christmas Present", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e74", "question": "Who played the blind character in the movie \"City Lights\"?", "answer": "Virginia Cherrill", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d74", "question": "What classic novel's subtitle is \"There and Back Again\"?", "answer": "The Hobbit", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "601b4c0e49076251badbeacc", "question": "Who got married in the very first White House wedding?", "answer": "Dolley Madison\u2019s sister -- Lucy Payne Washington, the sister of First Lady Dolley Madison, married Thomas Todd in 1819.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fedd9146ce05a3942286d78", "question": "What was the name of the last game released as a physical cartridge for the Super Nintendo?", "answer": "\"Fire Emblem: Thracia 776\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133afa5", "question": "Which oil rig exploded in 1988 killing 167 people?", "answer": "Piper Alpha", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339093", "question": "Who were the siblings of the Greek god Hades?", "answer": "Poseidon, Zeus, Hera, Demeter, Hestia", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "6015e7fdfe83fe1f2a824bd8", "question": "Who was the wife of the future Henry VIII\u2019s older brother, Arthur?", "answer": "Catherine of Aragon", "category": "history"}, {"id": "590721963745b36be73039f8", "question": "What were Frosty the Snowman\u2019s eyes made out of?", "answer": "Coal", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c0fc", "question": "Which word, taken from the French, translates literally as \"rotten pot\"?", "answer": "Potpourri", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133981f", "question": "All of the clocks in Pulp Fiction are stuck at what time?", "answer": "4:20", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59f9b82c364247bf200fb87c", "question": "For which game was the Steam Workshop service created to allow players to share modifications?", "answer": "Team Fortress 2", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338abb", "question": "Who was the valet that followed Phileas Fogg when he traveled around the world in 80 days?", "answer": "Jean Passepartout", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "59067a74ff9c0647b50a805a", "question": "In 2016, which vessel became the first solar-powered aircraft to circumnavigate the Earth?", "answer": "Solar Impulse 2", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c636", "question": "Which two features are longer on a hare than a rabbit?", "answer": "Legs and Ears", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b51f", "question": "What does the abbreviation HTML stand for?", "answer": "HyperText Markup Language", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c8a9", "question": "Trepanation is the practice of drilling holes where?", "answer": "In the skull", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5c90d0ee52800b05cac20f0f", "question": "What is Eisoptrophobia?", "answer": "The fear of mirrors", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339021", "question": "Whose autobiography's main title is \"True\"?", "answer": "Martin Kemp", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "600cc4416de0eb824d4052f1", "question": "What country's Indigenous name translates to \"Land of the Long White Cloud\"?", "answer": "New Zealand -- In the 1200s, Maori settlers called the North Island \"Aotearoa\", which translates to \"long white cloud\".", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b45a", "question": "Who led over 900 followers in a mass suicide in 1978?", "answer": "Jim Jones", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c67c", "question": "Bruxism is a medical term for when a person does what?", "answer": "Grinds their teeth", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe775fbeec85e375820b314", "question": "What constellation appears on the Alaskan flag?", "answer": "Ursa Major", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b6b4", "question": "What fruit is normally squeezed into a margarita?", "answer": "Lime", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339669", "question": "In the TV show \"The Simpsons\", which breed of dog is Santa's Little Helper?", "answer": "Greyhound", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a194", "question": "Raymond Burr played a journalist named Steve Martin in the American version of which giant monster movie?", "answer": "Godzilla, King of the Monsters", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "600a26b3e958e8c9f3127312", "question": "Which New England state produces the majority of the country\u2019s lobsters?", "answer": "Maine", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a54", "question": "What university presents the annual Pulitzer Prize journalism awards?", "answer": "Colombia", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133939c", "question": "Who plays the role of Captain John Miller in the movie \"Saving Private Ryan\"?", "answer": "Tom Hanks", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c2e2", "question": "How many days can a cockroach live up to without its head?", "answer": "9", "category": "science"}, {"id": "60121ae563c99d48cd169b09", "question": "An \"octothorpe\" refers to which popular social media symbol?", "answer": "Hashtag -- It is also called the \"pound sign\".", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a1b", "question": "Will Smith, Charlize Theron, and Jack Lemmon were all featured in what movie?", "answer": "The Legend of Bagger Vance", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339761", "question": "Which actress won an Oscar for her role in Monster's Ball?", "answer": "Halle Berry", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59ae94c1574a5ce6b56b824b", "question": "The cobnut is the fruit of what tree?", "answer": "Hazel", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5b32354fbf195a31e15d73ad", "question": "Which American comedian was born Benjamin Kubelsky?", "answer": "Jack Benny", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339bac", "question": "What band's first Top 10 hit in the US was 1984's \"Legs\"?", "answer": "ZZ Top", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c410", "question": "DuPont chemist Wallace Carothers developed what new plastic material in 1930?", "answer": "Nylon", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aad7", "question": "Which river is dammed by the Hoover Dam?", "answer": "Colorado River", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c27b", "question": "What does a panophobe fear?", "answer": "Everything", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c296", "question": "Who oversaw the design and assembly of the first atomic bomb?", "answer": "J. Robert Oppenheimer", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388f0", "question": "In the book \"Harry Potter and the Half Blood Prince\", who does Harry catch tentacula leaves?", "answer": "Professor Horace Slughorn", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b6ff", "question": "What decade was the first Indianapolis 500 race held in?", "answer": "1910s", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e7a", "question": "During what war was the novel \"M*A*S*H\" set?", "answer": "Korean War", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113394a5", "question": "In what century was the original Star Trek set?", "answer": "The 23rd century", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339aa7", "question": "What actress starred simultaneously on \"Dynasty\" and \"T.J. Hooker\" during the  early 1980s?", "answer": "Heather Locklear", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c1f3", "question": "What year marked the debut of the Volkswagen Golf GTI?", "answer": "1976", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b9c8", "question": "\"To swoon\" is to what?", "answer": "Faint", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338fe9", "question": "Who wrote the book \"The Prisoner of Zenda\"?", "answer": "Anthony Hope", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339815", "question": "What nickname was given to jazz trombonist Joe Nanton?", "answer": "Tricky Sam", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba2c", "question": "Which US state's official flower is the Saguato Cactus?", "answer": "Arizona", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fed2bbaec223966ae8f8911", "question": "What is the name of the smelly green ghost in \"Ghostbusters\"?", "answer": "Slimer", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133951c", "question": "Who was the second actor in history to decline an Oscar?", "answer": "Marlon Brando", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339fba", "question": "What smash video features a vintage performance by the fictional band The Love Below?", "answer": "Hey Ya!", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f0311338940", "question": "What do the boys use to start a signal fire in the book \"Lord of the Flies\"?", "answer": "Piggy's glasses", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a6f9", "question": "Hollywood is a district of what US city?", "answer": "Los Angeles", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a9b", "question": "What English author wrote the 1923 book \"Kangaroo\"?", "answer": "D.H. Lawrence", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "600242d04be4723ccac2218d", "question": "Holden Caulfield is the antihero of which 1945 classic novel?", "answer": "\"Catcher in the Rye\"", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bb5d", "question": "What ice cream chain once sold a ketchup-flavored ice cream?", "answer": "Baskin-Robbins", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc27", "question": "What popular figure was born Martha Helen Kostyra in 1941?", "answer": "Martha Stewart", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133aebe", "question": "Who was shot as he left the Washington Hilton in 1981?", "answer": "Ronald Reagan", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c250", "question": "What do you call an animal that eats both plants and animals?", "answer": "An Omnivore", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113395a2", "question": "Why is Max mad in the 1979 movie \"Mad Max\"?", "answer": "His wife and child were murdered", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "600f747fa9e54d890926f6f8", "question": "What is the name for the monetary unit used in Thailand?", "answer": "Thai Bhat", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133acb7", "question": "How many main islands make up the state of Hawaii?", "answer": "Eight", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b5fd", "question": "Which mint was the first to be used as a gum flavoring by the Wrigley Company?", "answer": "Spearmint", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59008be9cf842fa4c4ba969b", "question": "The Gobi Desert lies within which two countries?", "answer": "China and Mongolia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fdc0c2a469bb8041d07a04e", "question": "Which U.S. sandwich shop originally went by the name \"Pete's Super Submarines\"?", "answer": "Subway", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe8aa2501dd7bf43be5e758", "question": "\"Cohen\" is Hebrew for what?", "answer": "Priest", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe3ed658b5801b8f54a7fb1", "question": "From 1960 to 1965, which African country was a major area of Chinese political influence?", "answer": "Central African Republic", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113393c2", "question": "How many US soldiers were killed in the movie \"Black Hawk Down\"?", "answer": "18", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a89e", "question": "What islands are home to most of the world's blue-footed boobies?", "answer": "The Galapagos Islands", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c1dc", "question": "What are the two main ingredients of a Hollandaise sauce?\u00a0", "answer": "Egg yolks and liquid butter", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133af00", "question": "Who was the 16th president of the US?", "answer": "Abraham Lincoln", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ff2566b31a458464a93c460", "question": "What is traditional bubble gum made of?", "answer": "Chicle", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fef92f66ce05a3942286e89", "question": "Who provides the voice of Pikachu in the 2019 \"Pok\u00e9mon: Detective Pikachu\" movie?", "answer": "Ryan Reynolds", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c6e5", "question": "What French scientist discovered that many diseases are caused by germs?", "answer": "Louis Pasteur", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fea3d8fff048f679a45ab4f", "question": "Which insect is the closest relative to the grasshopper?", "answer": "Cockroach", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ad20", "question": "Which confectioner invented the heart-shaped Valentine's Day candy box?", "answer": "Richard Cadbury", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113398c4", "question": "What opera, composed by John Adams, was inspired by Richard Nixon?", "answer": "Nixon in China", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a8b2", "question": "In what city would you find Champ de Mars?", "answer": "Paris", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c2b0", "question": "What do the Scoville Heat Units indicate?", "answer": "The amount of capsaicin present", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe6a13620565ad31a57c7a1", "question": "What is the lowest natural point on Earth?", "answer": "The Challenger Deep", "category": "history"}, {"id": "601369741381754895396370", "question": "Which American poet won a Grammy for writing a Johnny Cash song?", "answer": "Shel Silverstein -- Best known for children's literature, he also wrote Johnny Cash's country hit, \"A Boy Named Sue\" in 1969.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a950", "question": "What is the only US state with only one syllable?", "answer": "Maine", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a5f2", "question": "On which river does Washington D.C. stand?", "answer": "The Potomac", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c2d", "question": "What US city was singer, Diana Ross, born in?", "answer": "Detroit", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ad9", "question": "In 1997, what country singer formed the band, The Ranch, with two fellow Australian musicians?", "answer": "Keith Urban", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133cad2", "question": "What is nephology the study of?", "answer": "Clouds", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c9ae", "question": "What do x and y chromosomes combine in making?", "answer": "Males", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339208", "question": "What pop star posed naked and pregnant on the August 2006 cover of Harper's Bazaar?", "answer": "Britney Spears", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d80", "question": "Who was the real-life model for the character of Matthew Harrison Brady in the novel \"Inherit the Wind\"?", "answer": "William Jennings Bryan", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133afbb", "question": "Which former US president was a Peanut Farmer?", "answer": "Jimmy Carter", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a51f", "question": "What are the four largest islands of Japan?", "answer": "Honshu, Kyushu, Shikoku, Hokkaido", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "600cc5cb6de0eb824d4052f4", "question": "What do Spaniards call a bullfight?", "answer": "Corrida", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5bfdffddb668d7dfe168b5bc", "question": "Chablis wine comes from which French wine region?", "answer": "Burgundy", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aaa5", "question": "Minsk is the capital of which European country?", "answer": "Belarus", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133998b", "question": "What was the name of the main police detective played by Jack Webb on the TV show \"Dragnet\"?", "answer": "Joe Friday", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe12f35e39efa6330e0fed7", "question": "Where is the world's shortest commercial runway?", "answer": "Saba", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bbad", "question": "What two words did Jim Henson combine to come up with the word \"muppet\"?", "answer": "marionette and puppet", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b35e", "question": "What was the first country to have a public monorail system?", "answer": "UK", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a96", "question": "\"The Tortelli's\" was the first attempt at a spin-off from what TV show?", "answer": "Cheers", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe657b5ae7e414034b5aee1", "question": "In the \"Book of Malachi\", God says that he has left the kingdom of Esau to which animals?", "answer": "Jackals", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "590498cccf93664eb104868b", "question": "What did Frosty the Snow man have for a nose?", "answer": "A button", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339fe8", "question": "What children's TV character lived in the Treasure House?", "answer": "Captain Kangaroo", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133adec", "question": "What year was the computer mouse first patented?", "answer": "1970", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe4b59a06d333868d34d6ea", "question": "Which country's troops withdrew from the Lebanese security zone after 22 years of occupation in 2000?", "answer": "Israel", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388c8", "question": "Who created the character Hercule Poirot?", "answer": "Agatha Christie", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b94f", "question": "What sport did hall-of-famer Mickey Mantle play?", "answer": "Baseball", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a8d0", "question": "In what country would you find the mouths of the river Nile?", "answer": "Egypt", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe7c2c5877e98cb9777898d", "question": "What city was known as and almost permanently named \"Batmania\"?", "answer": "Melbourne, Australia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b223", "question": "What city was JonBenet Ramsey killed in?", "answer": "Boulder, Colorado", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f97", "question": "What were the dolls in the novel \"Valley of the Dolls\"?", "answer": "Pills", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b04f", "question": "What holiday was first celebrated in Spokane, Washington on June 19, 1910?", "answer": "Father's Day", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ffa4019c73aa70ea0b70b07", "question": "Which district in central Tokyo is particularly famous for its electronics?", "answer": "Akihabara", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c2bb", "question": "What is a league?", "answer": "A unit of length", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113390a2", "question": "In Greek mythology, who are Demeter's siblings?", "answer": "Poseidon, Zeus, Hades, Hera, Hestia, Chiron", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a491", "question": "Which country do Belgium, France and Germany border?", "answer": "Luxembourg", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c4e2", "question": "What fruit comes in Redhaven and Harmony variety?", "answer": "Peaches", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5cd40cd3685cf15b733e9891", "question": "How many notes are there on a standard grand piano?", "answer": "88", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe7c86b877e98cb977789e4", "question": "Where can you see the petroglyphs of Newspaper Rock?", "answer": "Petrified Forrest National Park", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "58d077f4870e6f05ba600869", "question": "What role did Matthew McConaughey play in the 1995 film \"Boys on the Side\"?", "answer": "Abe Lincoln", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338fd9", "question": "In Shakespeare's \"Merchant of Venice\", who was Shylocks wife?", "answer": "Leah", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe7cd86877e98cb97778a38", "question": "Which US state hosts the world lumberjack championship?", "answer": "Wisconsin", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bb57", "question": "What British entrepreneur sold his Virgin Music Group to Thorn EMI in 1992?", "answer": "Richard Branson", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59e6b752fb6c85e9e634ff4b", "question": "What does \"Rx\" mean to a pharmacist?", "answer": "A medical prescription", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe7c690877e98cb977789bb", "question": "Where can you find the \"Dancing House\"?", "answer": "Prague, Czech Republic", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e8e", "question": "In Botticelli's \"The Birth of Venus\", what is Venus standing on as she rides to shore?", "answer": "A seashell", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c699", "question": "What bird gets its pink color from the algae and shrimp it eats?", "answer": "The flamingo", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ad84", "question": "Who was the first Russian Czar to westernize Russia?", "answer": "Peter I", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339449", "question": "How much are the guns worth in the 1998 movie \"Lock, Stock and Two Smoking Barrels\"?", "answer": "$250,000", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "60078261bd51d85e222ab657", "question": "What artist believed he was a reincarnation of his dead brother?", "answer": "When he was five, Dali's parents told him he was a reincarnation of his older brother, who died nine months before he was born.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133953d", "question": "Which one of the Salinger brothers developed an alcohol problem on \"Party of Five\"?", "answer": "Bailey", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "594d08181a1c922dd1ac64bf", "question": "Ulaanbaatar is the capital of which country?", "answer": "Mongolia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133afe6", "question": "The US Midwest experienced a severe drought known as the Dust Bowl, during what decade?", "answer": "1930s", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe8b1cc01dd7bf43be5e795", "question": "What is someone who is \"making a mountain out of a molehill\" doing?", "answer": "Exaggerating a minor problem", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c836", "question": "Before the 2004 launch of Space Ship One, who was the last American ever to go into space alone?", "answer": "Gordon Cooper", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe65619ae7e414034b5aec0", "question": "What was Atlas famously forced to do by the Greek gods?", "answer": "Hold the Heavens on his shoulders", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338b89", "question": "What is the number of thieves that Alibaba had?", "answer": "40", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113396cb", "question": "Who played the role of Dr. Frasier Crane in the TV show \"Frasier\"?", "answer": "Kelsey Grammer", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe52f451bf59ab7d2e38113", "question": "What direction does the Statue of Liberty face?", "answer": "Southeast", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ab1a", "question": "What European country is the Arch of Hadrian located in?", "answer": "Greece", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5a9e94177ccba3ffe45786ce", "question": "How old was Buddy Holly when he died in a plane crash in 1959?", "answer": "22 years old", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fecc82eec223966ae8f888f", "question": "Which professional sport in the United States commonly has multiple games on Christmas Day?", "answer": "NBA", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b935", "question": "What are you shopping for if you're sized up by a Brannock device?", "answer": "Shoes", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5bb35b4f2627b8fe95581beb", "question": "In ABC's \"Once Upon a Time\" what character was played by Colin O' Donoghue?", "answer": "Captain Hook", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf39", "question": "How many ring are there on the olympic flag?", "answer": "Five", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133afe5", "question": "Who did George Bush Sr. defeat in the election in 1988?", "answer": "Michael Dukakis", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133944a", "question": "Who played the role of Shoeless Joe Jackson in the 1989 movie \"Field of Dreams\"?", "answer": "Ray Liotta", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b42d", "question": "What year did Alfred Hitchcock become a citizen of the United States?", "answer": "1955", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ae4b", "question": "Who did Harry Truman dismiss as commander of the UN forces in Korea in 1951?", "answer": "General Douglas MacArthur", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a662", "question": "What region was explored by Vitus Bering?", "answer": "Arctic", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339566", "question": "Who directed, The Christmas Kid\"?", "answer": "Sid PInk", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ab23", "question": "Which ocean does Mozambique has water access to?", "answer": "Indian", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "597cd9a4e347d002c297e4cd", "question": "In modern badminton, how many points typically win a singles game?", "answer": "21", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59a1a4e212f2a7826b9b8733", "question": "Which Panamanian boxer's nickname, translated into English, means \"Hands of Stone\"?", "answer": "Roberto Duran", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113398c5", "question": "Who composed the song \"Rhapsody in Blue\"?", "answer": "George Gershwin", "category": "entertainment"}]